const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'What is the most important principle to keep in mind whilst skiing?',
        answers: [
            'Take advantage of all the ski resort has to offer',
            'Respect of the mountain + the people around you',
            'How to carve up the fresh pow - yew!',
            'To get down the mountain as fast as possible.'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Respect of the mountain + the people around you',
        icon: 'https://media1.giphy.com/media/SC0VDXns3gvS0/giphy.gif?cid=3640f6095c6e37d2646a444873f50222',
        alt: 'man ski dancing'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who has the right of way when sharing the hill',
        answers: [
            'Everyone - its a freefall! Wooooooo',
            'The person who’s shorter in height',
            'Whoever calls “My way” first',
            'The person skiing or boarding below you'

        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The person skiing or boarding below you',
        icon: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/3o6Mb7ZPkxTtk6LoD6/giphy.gif',
        alt: 'Homer Simpson skiing badly'
    },
    {
        question: 'If you need to stop whilst on your way down the mountain, its best to...',
        answers: [
            'Dive in to the nearest powder pile',
            'Wait where you are very visible, but where others have enough space to avoid you',
            'Right in the middle of the slope',
            'Scream and shout ‘I’m here'

        ],
        correctAnswer:  'Wait where you are very visible, but where others have enough space to avoid you',
        icon: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/X4sbcP4xNXTY4/giphy.gif',
        alt: 'water skiing squirrel'
    },
    {
        question: 'You come across someone that is laying on the ground on their own and appears to have injured themselves… the first thing you should do is:',
        answers: [
           'Stick your poles in a cross shape uphill to alert other skiers to not ski into them, ask anyone going down to the nearest chair lift to call for ski patrol assistance.',
            'Try moving the injured out of the way',
            'Tell the injured person a joke to cheer them up',
            'Tell the injured person a story about when you injured yourself on the mountain.',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Stick your poles in a cross shape uphill to alert other skiers to not ski into them, ask anyone going down to the nearest chair lift to call for ski patrol assistance.',
        icon: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/3o6Mblm3wZ0UdGFrk4/giphy.gif',
        alt: 'powder skiier'
    },
    {
        question: 'Whilst preparing for a day of skiing, you should always remember to bring',
        answers: [
            
        'Bug spray, sun tanning oil, a pink flamingo floatie and bluetooth speaker',
        'Surf board, flower necklace, flask of vodka and flip flops',
        'SPF, water, snacks, a cell phone and a buddy',
        'your macbook',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'SPF, water, snacks, a cell phone and a buddy',
        icon: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/nA94mGik3RAZy/giphy.gif',
        alt: 'skier on the ground struggling to get up'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the number one rule of overtaking others on the mountain?',
        answers: [
        'Make sure to scream -overtaking slow-poke!',
        'Be as quiet as possible',
        'Make sure that you leave enough room when overtaking others for any voluntary or involuntary movements that they may make.',
        'Sing your fave song',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Make sure that you leave enough room when overtaking others for any voluntary or involuntary movements that they may make.',
        icon: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/2Ysf8gLdO0fZSTBW8A/giphy.gif',
        alt: 'monkey on skis'
    },
    {
        question: 'When should you learn the rules of riding a lift?',
        answers: [
            'After the lift',
            'Ask the lift operator as you are in line for the lift',
            'Before you go on your first lift',
            'Mid-lift',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Before you go on your first lift',
        icon: 'https://media1.giphy.com/media/SC0VDXns3gvS0/giphy.gif?cid=3640f6095c6e37d2646a444873f50222',
        alt: 'Man dancing on skis'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the most important thing to control on the mountain',
        answers: [
            'How many cliff bars you have in your pocket',
            'How much fun you’re having',
            'Your speed - You must be in control, and adapt your speed and manner of skiing to your ability and the prevailing conditions of terrain, snow and weather, as well as to the density of other skiers.',
            'Make sure you’re getting the most runs in',

        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Your speed - You must be in control, and adapt your speed and manner of skiing to your ability and the prevailing conditions of terrain, snow and weather, as well as to the density of other skiers.',
        icon: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/AQePBH7QRLPYk/giphy.gif',
        alt: 'skiier carving'
    },
    {
        question: 'When backcountry skiing, an essential iteam to take is a...',
        answers: [
            'Bacon',
            'Beaven',
            'Beacan',
            'Brolly',

        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Beacan',
        icon: 'https://media1.giphy.com/media/SC0VDXns3gvS0/giphy.gif?cid=3640f6095c6e37d2646a444873f50222',
        alt: 'dog on skis'
    },
    {
        question: 'If you are considering skiing off piste markings, the number one rule is',
        answers: [
            'Go as fast as humanly possible',
            'Enjoy the trees and natural wildlife',
            'Don’t go alone, always take a buddy',
            'Make a snowman with the fresh pow',

        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Don’t go alone, always take a buddy',
        icon: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/5T4my7WOM7ER2/giphy.gif',
        alt: 'skiier flying in the air'
    }
]